businesswire.com 2008-12-22

# Privacy Statement | Business Wire

**Last updated September 12, 2008**

Business Wire is committed to providing its online users with services and information in an efficient and secure manner. This privacy policy explains what personal information is collected on businesswire.com and eon.businesswire.com (the "Business Wire Web sites") from users of Business Wire's various online services, how that information is used and what measures Business Wire takes to safeguard its users' privacy.

**What personal information is collected on the Business Wire Web sites?**

There is no general registration requirement for users of the Business Wire Web sites. Instead, we only collect information as needed to provide you with particular services such as submitting releases, Media Services (PressPass and ExpertSource), and Company NewsCenter e-mail news alerts. Depending on the service you register for, we may collect some or all of the following information: name, e-mail address, street address, telephone and facsimile numbers, employer company profile, client profile, beat (for media users) and categories of interest.

In addition, Business Wire is required to collect credit card information for those parties purchasing products or services through the eon.businesswire.com site. This information is used solely for the processing of the specific purchase and is not used for any other purpose. Business Wire's method of collecting and processing credit card information is PCI-DSS compliant.

**How does Business Wire use the information collected on the Business Wire Web sites?**

Information about individual users collected on the Business Wire Web sites is used for internal business purposes, including customizing services, contacting members regarding submissions, and responding to requests for information. On occasion, Business Wire or one of its members or affiliates may also use this information to inform you of news, service upgrades or new services or products that may be of particular interest to you.

Business Wire tracks aggregate anonymous statistics regarding usage of the web sites and provides this anonymous information to members, affiliates, advertisers and for other lawful purposes.

**Does Business Wire provide personal information collected on the Business Wire Web sites to third parties?**

Business Wire does not sell, trade or rent personal information collected online and will not knowingly disclose any individual personal information to third parties except as follows:

(1) In order to provide you with requested services, Business Wire may provide contact or other necessary information to affiliated companies. For example, if you register for the Expertsource service, Business Wire may provide only your email address to the identified expert in order to facilitate initial contact between you and the relevant expert;

(2) If you register to have press releases for a particular Business Wire member's company in a Company NewsCenter e-mailed to you the member company may be notified that you have utilized one of these services and provided with your e-mail address in order to follow-up and provide you with additional information;

(3) When disclosure is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with the rights (including property rights) or safety of other users or third parties or of Business Wire; and

(4) When Business Wire reasonably believes that disclosure is required by law or to comply with legal process served on Business Wire.

**How can I change or update the information I provide at the Business Wire Web sites?**

Where user profile information is collected and stored in order to provide you with requested services, Business Wire offers you the opportunity to change or update your profile information at any time by visiting www.businesswire.com or eon.businesswire.com, whichever is applicable, and clicking on "My Profile" or "My Account".

For subscription services such as Expert News Alert e-mail news delivery, you may unsubscribe at any time by clicking on the "unsubscribe" button on the any email received.

**Do the Business Wire Web sites use cookies?**

Yes, however Business Wire only uses cookies to facilitate functions at the Business Wire Web sites and does not record or store any information about your movements on the Internet outside the Business Wire Web sites. Please note that if you click on a link to a third-party Web site from one of the Business Wire Web sites, the linked-to site may have different policies and practices with regard to cookies and Business Wire has no control over and is not responsible for such policies or practices. You should always consult the privacy policy governing any Web site you visit on the Internet for complete information about their policies and practices.

**What security measures does Business Wire take to safeguard its online users' privacy?**

Information you submit at a Business Wire Web site upon registration for specific services is password-protected so that the only parties who have access to the information besides Business Wire and its agents and affiliates are the member entity and its employees.

In addition, individual employees of members will receive individual passwords when they log-on to submit press releases online, and information submitted using the Business Wire Web sites is further protected by Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts the information during transmission.

In order to protect the integrity of the password system, members should refrain from disclosing passwords and immediately change any passwords that may have been compromised.

Business Wire will never ask you for your password by e-mail, so members and their employees should not respond to unsolicited e-mail requests asking for password information even if such requests appear to be from Business Wire.

Please be advised that no data transmission over the Internet is 100% secured. Business Wire is committed to protecting users' personal information, but cannot guarantee or warrant the security of this information when it is sent to or through the Business Wire Web sites. Transmission of such information is therefore at the risk of the user.

**Usernames and Passwords**

Users may register with www.businesswire.com and/or eon.businesswire.com. Once usernames and passwords (the "Login Information") are issued to users (the "Authorized Users"), the Authorized Users accept full responsibility for the use of the Login Information. The Authorized User may not, under any circumstances, release their Login Information to any other person for any reason, and is required to keep the Login Information strictly confidential. If any breach of security, theft or loss, or unauthorized disclosure of the Login Information occurs, the Authorized User must immediately notify Business Wire of such security breach.

**Privacy policy updates**

This policy will be updated from time to time as necessary to add new Business Wire Web sites to its coverage or to address new services and functions. Business Wire will provide you with notice of any changes or updates to this policy at the home page of each of the Business Wire Web sites.
